Finding Aid for the Paul Egly Papers LSC.1282
UCLA Library Special Collections
- "Correspondence and notes,. Some pleadings.", 1977-1979; [carton 3] (Box 7, Box 8, Box 9, Box 10, Box 11, Box 12, Box 13, Box 14, Box 15, Box 16, Box 17, Box 18, Box 19, Box 20, Box 21, Box 22, Box 23)
  - 2) John Caughey; Amicus curiae pleadings, [carton 11] (Box 25-26)
    - Respondent's Appeal Briefs, 1979 (Box 25-26)
    - Second Trial Exhibits Board 1-193 (Box 25-26)
    - Second Trial Duplicate Exhibits/Resurvee(?) (Box 25-26)
    - Second Trial Exhibits-UTLA, IP, Bustop (Box 25-26)
    - Second Trial Exhibits Petitioners (Box 25-26)
    - Respondent Pleadings and Exhibits (Box 25-26)
    - Monitoring Committee and Experts (Box 25-26)
    - Bustop, Best, UTLA, IP, Filings, S.E. Legal Aid (Box 25-26)
    - Monitoring Committee Miscellaneous (Box 25-26)
    - Egly Miscellaneous (Box 25-26)
    - Other Desegregation Pleadings/Special Monitors (Box 25-26)
    - Superior, Appellate, Superior and Decisions, Transcripts (Box 25-26)
    - Petitioners and Respondent's Exhibits (Box 25-26)
    - Respondent's Exhibits (Box 25-26)
    - Petitioner's Pleadings (Box 25-26)
    - Respondent's RIMS Exhibits (Box 25-26)
    - Respondent's Exhibits (Box 25-26)
    - Respondent's Filings (Box 25-26)
    - MAPS - Exhibits (Box 25-26)
  - Intervenors appellate briefs, [carton 4] (Box 27)
    - B.E.S.T. (Box 27)
      - DCA, Petition for Writ - Temporary Stay, 1980 September 12
      - Respondents Petition DCA, 1980 September 2
      - Application for Extended Time DCA, 1980 December 30
      - California Supreme Court Memorandum in Opposition to Petitioners Writ, 1980 September 9
      - U.S. Supreme Court Support of Application for Stay, 1980 September 10
      - DCA, Petition for Writ of, 1980 September 12
      - Superior, Notice of Appeal, 1980 August 11
      - DCA, Petition for Writ to Stay Court Order, 1980 August 4
    - U.T.L.A. (Box 27)
      - Petition for Writ, DCA, 1980 September 10
      - Appeal from Superior Court, DCA, 1980 November 5
      - Exhibit to Petition, DCA, 1980 September 10
      - Declaration of Kressner, DCA, 1980 September 17
    - Integration Project (Box 27)
      - Notice of Appeal, 1980 September 5
      - Supreme Court, California, Brief in Support of Caughey, 1980 August 26
    - Bustop (Box 27)
      - Reply to Application, U.S. Supreme Court, 1980 September 10
      - California Supreme Court, Opposition to Crawford's Emergency Petition, 1980 September 10
      - Reply Brief on Appeal July 7 Order, DCA, 1980 December 13
      - DCA Reply Brief re Proposition L, 1980 November 2
      - DCA, Memo Support Petition Writ, 1980
    - Caughey - Amicus brief (Box 27)
      - DCA, Application to file Amicus, 1980 November 14
      - Exhibits in Support of Brief, DCA, 1980 November 14
      - Request for Reconsideration, DCA, 1980 December 1
      - California Supreme Court, Amicus for Writ of Extraordinary Relief, 1980 August 11
    - Respondent appeal briefs, 1979; [carton 12] (Box 28, Box 29)
- Second trial, 1979 October - 1980 April; [cartons 13-18] (Box 30, Box 31, Box 32, Box 33, Box 34, Box 35, Box 36, Box 37, Box 38, Box 39, Box 40, Box 41, Box 42, Box 43)
  - Index to exhibits; Minute orders; Exhibit 11 (Box 30)
  - Exhibits 11 - 64 [1], except 60, 60A and 61 (Box 31)
  - Exhibits 64 [2] - 85 (Box 32)
  - Exhibits 86 - 191 (Box 33)
  - Exhibits 193 - 206; 60 (Box 34)
  - Exhibits 60A, 61 and duplicates 75 - 77 (Box 35)
  - Exhibits, duplicates 73, 74, 95, 145, 146, 196 - 199 (Box 36)
  - Racial and ethnic surveys, 1977, 1979 (Box 36)
  - Final report of the emergency School aid act (Box 36)
  - Magnet School Program, 1979 February 13 (Box 36)
  - "Duplicate Board exhibits.", [carton 15] (Box 37, Box 38)
  - "Duplicate Board exhibits"; Bustop exhibits, [cartons 16-17] (Box 39)
  - Exhibits: Bustop, UTLA and Integration Projects (Box 40)
  - Petitioners Exhibits (Box 41)
    Includes 300 series, White flight, enrollment, permits.
  - Petitioners exhibits (Box 42, Box 43)
    - "500 series" and 554 - 561 (Box 42)
    - RIMS, overcrowding, magnets, PWT and Wilshire complex (Box 43)
- Respondents Pleadings and exhibits, [carton 19] (Box 44, Box 45, Box 46)
  - 1977 (Box 44)
  - 1978-1979 (Box 45)
  - 1980 (Box 46)
- Monitoring Committee and experts reports, 1978-1979; [carton 20] (Box 47, Box 48, Box 49)
- "BEST, Bustop, UTLA, Integration Project Filings, Southeast Legal Aid.", [carton 21] (Box 50, Box 51)
- "Monitoring Committee and Egly misc[ellaneous].", [carton 22] (Box 52, Box 53)
- "Other desegregation pleadings. Special monitors correspondence (Hamilton, Rabinowitz and Stanton)", [carton 23] (Box 54, Box 55)
- "Superior Appellate, Supreme Court decisions. Transcripts.", [carton 24] (Box 55, Box 56, Box 57)
- "Petitioners' and respondents exhibits and lists", 1977; [carton 25] (Box 58)
- "Respondent exhibits", [carton 26] (Box 58, Box 59, Box 60)
- "Petitioners' pleadings", [carton 27] (Box 61, Box 62, Box 63)
- "Respondent's RIMS exhibits, 1979-1980", [carton 28] (Box 63, Othertype I)
- "Respondent's RIMS exhibits, 1979-1980" (Box 64, Othertype I-III)
- "Respondent's RIMS exhibits, 1979-1980" and related material (Box 65, Othertype II-VII)
- "Respondents' exhibits, 1977-1980", [carton 29] (Box 66, Box 67, Box 68)
- "Monitoring Committee Referee Simulations" (Box 68, Box 69, Box 70)
- RIMS materials, [Duplicates?] (Box 71)
- LAUSD proposals, 1977, 1979 (Box 72, Box 73, Box 74)
- Letters and tabulation of contributions re Senator Robbins anti-busing bill (Box 74)
- CACSI report and related material, 1977 (Box 75)
- Miscellany re LAUSD (Box 76)
  Includes 1979/1980 Final Budget, Answers to 22 questions and Board exhibits, 1977 and maps found with loose correspondence now in Box 100.
- "Petitioners' filings" (Box 76, Box 77, Box 78)
- "Simulations" (Box 79, Box 80, Box 81)
- "Duplicate filings" (Box 82, Box 83, Box 84)
- Referee's (Monroe E. Price) reports, 1977-1980 (Box 85)
- CACSI and LAUSD reports, (duplicates) (Box 86)
- Books - Not Hostility and Violence program materials (Box 87)
- Miscellaneous correspondence from the public (Box 87)
- Miscellaneous court records (Box 87)
- Folders "Attorney fees." (Box 88)
- Miscellaneous correspondence from the public (Box 88)
- "Respondents' Filings, 1979-1981." (Box 89, Box 90, Box 91)
- "LAUSD March 1979 Filing", [duplicates?] (Box 92)
- Experts reports, with manuscript annotations, 1979 (Box 93)
- "Cases, other cities, articles." (Box 94, Box 95)
- "Desegregation articles", 1970s (Box 96)
  Includes listing in first folder.
- "School profiles." (Box 96, Box 97, Box 98)
- Monitoring Committee, observers' reports (Box 99)
- Correspondence from the public (Box 99, Box 100)
- Correspondence from the public (Box 101, Box 102)
  Includes some arranged files with Egly's reply.
- Correspondence from the Monitoring Committee (Box 102)
- Court copies of simulation supplements, file 1A. (Box 102)
  [Map: for rest of related files, see oversize packages 13-14]
- Supplement to the second series of simulations of desegregation plans (Box 102)
- Parker Directory of Attorneys, 1979 (Box 102)
- West's California Digest, 1978 July (Box 102)
- LAUSD plan: "Integrated educational excellence through choice", 1977 October 3; [duplicates?] (Box 103, Box 104, Box 105)
  - Appendices I and II (Box 103)
  - Appendices III - V (part) (Box 104)
  - Appendices V (end) - VI (Box 105)
  - Copy of the plan, 1977 October 3; manuscript annotations in (?) Judge Egly's handwriting (Box 105)
- LAUSD plan: "Plan for the Integration of people in the Los Angeles Unified School District", 1977 March 18; [Duplicate?] (Box 105, Volume I-II (part))
- LAUSD plan: "Plan for the integration of pupils in the Los Angeles Unified School District", 1977 March 18; [Duplicate?] (Box 106, Volume II (end)-III)
- LAUSD plan in response to court order of February 7, 1978: "Integrated education excellence through choice", [Duplicates?] (Box 106, Box 107)
  - 1979 March 12 (Box 106, Volume I-II)
  - 1979 March 12 (Box 107, Volume III-VI)
- Various pleadings, [Duplicates?] (Box 107)
- Unlisted (Box 108, Box 109, Box 110)
- Rolled plans (Box 114, Box 115, Box 116)
- "Appendices A, B, and C, Report to Judge Egly by Bernard R. Gifford, November 6, 1978" (Box 111)
- "Court copies of simulation supplements", 1980; [computer print-out] (Box 112, Box 113, Box 114)
- Two charts, "Nonsegregated and segregated Schools", [map folder] (Box 116)
- Miscellaneous charts (Box 114)